-(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
-♪ ("OH YES" BY OHNO PLAYS) ♪
AMANDA SEALES:  I grew up
with all the white people.
No one is telling them
about their problematic
behaviors.
(WHIP SMACKS)
AMANDA:  Tonight's the night.
♪ Haters talk like
Rose this, rose that ♪
AMANDA: There are people
watching this that
just found out
there's a Negro national anthem,
and that it is not a song
from Hamilton.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
♪ Paper chase ambition ♪
You know, black women...
we are the masters
at compliments.
We don't even say
a full sentence.
Okay, polka dots!
When you a black person
in any office, you stay ready.
'Cause you're always wondering
on a scale of Stacey Dash
to Nat Turner...
(FORCEFULLY) "How black am I
gon' have to get?"
♪ Y'all just never listen ♪
(SINGING)
♪ What are we talking about? ♪
This is...
-(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
-♪ (VOCALIZING) ♪